{
  "2025-12-21": {
    "Geography": {
      "question": "Top 10 countries by population",
      "answers": ["China","India","USA","Indonesia","Pakistan","Brazil","Nigeria","Bangladesh","Russia","Mexico"]
    },
    "History": {
      "question": "Top 10 historical events by number of casualties",
      "answers": ["WWII","Taiping Rebellion","World War I","Mongol Conquests","Napoleonic Wars","An Lushan Rebellion","Thirty Years' War","Qing conquest of Ming","Russian Civil War","Chinese Civil War"]
    },
    "General Knowledge": {
      "question": "Top 10 highest mountains in the world",
      "answers": ["Mount Everest","K2","Kangchenjunga","Lhotse","Makalu","Cho Oyu","Dhaulagiri","Manaslu","Nanga Parbat","Annapurna"]
    },
    "Soccer": {
      "question": "Top 10 Manchester United all-time appearances",
      "answers": ["Ryan Giggs","Bobby Charlton","Paul Scholes","Bill Foulkes","Gary Neville","Wayne Rooney","Denis Irwin","Alex Stepney","Edwin van der Sar","Eric Cantona"]
    },
    "American Football": {
      "question": "Top 10 NFL quarterbacks by career passing yards",
      "answers": ["Tom Brady","Drew Brees","Peyton Manning","Brett Favre","Ben Roethlisberger","Philip Rivers","Matt Ryan","Dan Marino","Eli Manning","John Elway"]
    }
  },
  "2025-12-22": {
    "Geography": {
      "question": "Top 10 longest rivers in the world",
      "answers": ["Nile","Amazon","Yangtze","Mississippi","Yenisei","Yellow River","Ob","Parana","Congo","Amur"]
    },
    "History": {
      "question": "Top 10 US Presidents by time in office",
      "answers": ["Franklin D. Roosevelt","Dwight D. Eisenhower","Woodrow Wilson","Thomas Jefferson","James Madison","James Monroe","Andrew Jackson","George Washington","Harry S. Truman","Abraham Lincoln"]
    },
    "General Knowledge": {
      "question": "Top 10 largest deserts by area",
      "answers": ["Sahara","Arabian","Gobi","Kalahari","Patagonian","Great Victoria","Great Basin","Syrian","Thar","Sonoran"]
    },
    "Soccer": {
      "question": "Top 10 footballers by international goals scored",
      "answers": ["Cristiano Ronaldo","Lionel Messi","Luis Suarez","Andres Iniesta","Xavi Hernandez","Ronaldinho","Zlatan Ibrahimovic","Paolo Maldini","Thierry Henry","Francesco Totti"]
    },
    "American Football": {
      "question": "Top 10 NFL running backs by career rushing yards",
      "answers": ["Emmitt Smith","Walter Payton","Barry Sanders","Frank Gore","LaDainian Tomlinson","Marcus Allen","Earl Campbell","Marshall Faulk","Jim Brown","Curtis Martin"]
    }
  },
  "2025-12-23": {
    "Geography": {
      "question": "Top 10 largest cities by population",
      "answers": ["Tokyo","Delhi","Shanghai","Sao Paulo","Mumbai","Beijing","Mexico City","Osaka","Cairo","New York City"]
    },
    "History": {
      "question": "Top 10 deadliest battles by number of troops involved",
      "answers": ["Battle of Stalingrad","Battle of the Somme","Battle of Verdun","Battle of Gettysburg","Battle of Waterloo","Battle of Kursk","Battle of Leipzig","Battle of Borodino","Battle of Hastings","Battle of Midway"]
    },
    "General Knowledge": {
      "question": "Top 10 fastest animals by recorded speed",
      "answers": ["Cheetah (≈120 km/h)","Peregrine Falcon (389 km/h)","Sailfish (≈110 km/h)","Pronghorn (≈88 km/h)","Springbok (≈88 km/h)","Lion (≈80 km/h)","Thomson's Gazelle (≈80 km/h)","Greyhound (≈72 km/h)","Brown Hare (≈72 km/h)","Kangaroo (≈71 km/h)"]
    },
    "Soccer": {
      "question": "Top 10 footballers by UEFA Champions League appearances",
      "answers": ["Iker Casillas","Raul Gonzalez","Sergio Ramos","Fernando Hierro","Roberto Carlos","Zinedine Zidane","Cristiano Ronaldo","Karim Benzema","Luka Modric","Luis Figo"]
    },
    "American Football": {
      "question": "Top 10 NFL wide receivers by career receptions",
      "answers": ["Jerry Rice","Larry Fitzgerald","Terrell Owens","Randy Moss","Marvin Harrison","Steve Largent","Isaac Bruce","Andre Johnson","Antonio Brown","Michael Thomas"]
    }
  },
  "2025-12-24": {
    "Geography": {
      "question": "Top 10 largest islands by area",
      "answers": ["Greenland","New Guinea","Borneo","Madagascar","Baffin Island","Sumatra","Honshu","Great Britain","Victoria Island","Ellesmere Island"]
    },
    "History": {
      "question": "Top 10 longest-reigning historical leaders",
      "answers": ["Louis XIV","Queen Elizabeth II","Fidel Castro","King Bhumibol Adulyadej","Emperor Hirohito","Peter the Great","Queen Victoria","Franz Joseph I","George III","Charlemagne"]
    },
    "General Knowledge": {
      "question": "Top 10 tallest buildings in the world",
      "answers": ["Burj Khalifa","Shanghai Tower","Abraj Al-Bait Clock Tower","Ping An Finance Center","Lotte World Tower","One World Trade Center","Guangzhou CTF Finance Centre","Tianjin CTF Finance Center","Taipei 101","CITIC Tower"]
    },
    "Soccer": {
      "question": "Top 10 Liverpool FC all-time appearances",
      "answers": ["Steven Gerrard","Ian Rush","Fernando Torres","Robbie Fowler","Paul Scholes","Ryan Giggs","Wayne Rooney","Roy Keane","Bryan Robson","David Beckham"]
    },
    "American Football": {
      "question": "Top 10 NFL quarterbacks by career wins",
      "answers": ["Tom Brady","Joe Montana","Peyton Manning","Brett Favre","Drew Brees","Ben Roethlisberger","Dan Marino","Aaron Rodgers","John Elway","Patrick Mahomes"]
    }
  },
  "2025-12-25": {
    "Geography": {
      "question": "Top 10 highest mountains by elevation",
      "answers": ["Mount Everest","K2","Kangchenjunga","Lhotse","Makalu","Cho Oyu","Dhaulagiri","Manaslu","Nanga Parbat","Annapurna"]
    },
    "History": {
      "question": "Top 10 historical empires by land area",
      "answers": ["British Empire","Mongol Empire","Russian Empire","Qing Dynasty","Umayyad Caliphate","Roman Empire","Ottoman Empire","Spanish Empire","Abbasid Caliphate","Maurya Empire"]
    },
    "General Knowledge": {
      "question": "Top 10 longest rivers in the world",
      "answers": ["Amazon","Nile","Yangtze","Mississippi","Yenisei","Yellow River","Ob","Parana","Congo","Amur"]
    },
    "Soccer": {
      "question": "Top 10 footballers by international goals",
      "answers": ["Lionel Messi","Cristiano Ronaldo","Luis Suarez","Andres Iniesta","Xavi Hernandez","Ronaldinho","Zlatan Ibrahimovic","Paolo Maldini","Thierry Henry","Francesco Totti"]
    },
    "American Football": {
      "question": "Top 10 NFL running backs by career rushing yards",
      "answers": ["Emmitt Smith","Walter Payton","Barry Sanders","Frank Gore","LaDainian Tomlinson","Marcus Allen","Earl Campbell","Marshall Faulk","Jim Brown","Curtis Martin"]
    }
  },
  "2025-12-26": {
    "Geography": {
      "question": "Top 10 countries by land area",
      "answers": ["USA","China","India","Brazil","Russia","Canada","Australia","Argentina","Kazakhstan","Algeria"]
    },
    "History": {
      "question": "Top 10 longest-reigning monarchs in history",
      "answers": ["Louis XIV","Queen Elizabeth II","King Bhumibol Adulyadej","Emperor Hirohito","Franz Joseph I","Johann II of Liechtenstein","Queen Victoria","Pedro II of Brazil","Charles III of Spain","King Sobhuza II"]
    },
    "General Knowledge": {
      "question": "Top 10 largest deserts by area",
      "answers": ["Sahara","Gobi","Kalahari","Arabian","Patagonian","Great Victoria","Great Basin","Syrian","Thar","Sonoran"]
    },
    "Soccer": {
      "question": "Top 10 footballers by club goals scored",
      "answers": ["Cristiano Ronaldo","Lionel Messi","Zlatan Ibrahimovic","Luis Suarez","Karim Benzema","Neymar","Kylian Mbappe","Harry Kane","Sergio Aguero","Robert Lewandowski"]
    },
    "American Football": {
      "question": "Top 10 NFL quarterbacks by career passing yards",
      "answers": ["Tom Brady","Drew Brees","Peyton Manning","Brett Favre","Ben Roethlisberger","Aaron Rodgers","Matt Ryan","Joe Montana","Dan Marino","Patrick Mahomes"]
    }
  },
  "2025-12-27": {
    "Geography": {
      "question": "Top 10 largest cities by population",
      "answers": ["Tokyo","Delhi","Shanghai","Sao Paulo","Mumbai","Beijing","Mexico City","Osaka","Cairo","New York City"]
    },
    "History": {
      "question": "Top 10 deadliest battles by casualties",
      "answers": ["Battle of Normandy","Battle of Bulge","Battle of Britain","Battle of Midway","Battle of Kursk","Battle of Iwo Jima","Battle of Thermopylae","Battle of Gettysburg","Battle of Agincourt","Battle of Hastings"]
    },
    "General Knowledge": {
      "question": "Top 10 highest mountains on each continent",
      "answers": ["Mount Kilimanjaro","Mount Elbrus","Mount Denali","Mount Aconcagua","Mount Vinson","Mount Puncak Jaya","Mount Kosciuszko","Mount Fuji","Mount St. Elias","Mount Logan"]
    },
    "Soccer": {
      "question": "Top 10 footballers by UEFA Champions League appearances",
      "answers": ["Iker Casillas","Raul Gonzalez","Sergio Ramos","Fernando Hierro","Roberto Carlos","Zinedine Zidane","Cristiano Ronaldo","Karim Benzema","Luka Modric","Luis Figo"]
    },
    "American Football": {
      "question": "Top 10 NFL wide receivers by career receptions",
      "answers": ["Jerry Rice","Larry Fitzgerald","Terrell Owens","Randy Moss","Marvin Harrison","Steve Largent","Isaac Bruce","Andre Johnson","Antonio Brown","Michael Thomas"]
    }
  },
  "2025-12-28": {
    "Geography": {
      "question": "Top 10 largest islands by area",
      "answers": ["Greenland","New Guinea","Borneo","Madagascar","Baffin Island","Sumatra","Honshu","Great Britain","Victoria Island","Ellesmere Island"]
    },
    "History": {
      "question": "Top 10 explorers by territories discovered",
      "answers": ["Christopher Columbus","Marco Polo","Ferdinand Magellan","Vasco da Gama","Amerigo Vespucci","James Cook","Hernan Cortes","Francisco Pizarro","Henry Hudson","Leif Erikson"]
    },
    "General Knowledge": {
      "question": "Top 10 most influential scientists by discoveries",
      "answers": ["Marie Curie","Albert Einstein","Isaac Newton","Niels Bohr","Galileo Galilei","Nikola Tesla","Stephen Hawking","Richard Feynman","Michael Faraday","James Clerk Maxwell"]
    },
    "Soccer": {
      "question": "Top 10 footballers by club appearances",
      "answers": ["Gianluigi Buffon","Paolo Maldini","Francesco Totti","Andrea Pirlo","Alessandro Del Piero","Roberto Baggio","Franco Baresi","Carlo Ancelotti","Gennaro Gattuso","Christian Vieri"]
    },
    "American Football": {
      "question": "Top 10 NFL kickers by career points scored",
      "answers": ["Adam Vinatieri","Morten Andersen","Justin Tucker","Gary Anderson","Stephen Gostkowski","David Akers","John Carney","Matt Stover","Jason Hanson","Sebastian Janikowski"]
    }
  },
  "2025-12-29": {
    "Geography": {
      "question": "Top 10 deepest ocean trenches",
      "answers": ["Mariana Trench","Tonga Trench","Philippine Trench","Kuril-Kamchatka Trench","Japan Trench","Kermadec Trench","Puerto Rico Trench","Java Trench","South Sandwich Trench","Sunda Trench"]
    },
    "History": {
      "question": "Top 10 wars by number of deaths",
      "answers": ["World War I","World War II","Vietnam War","Korean War","Napoleonic Wars","American Civil War","Crimean War","Russo-Japanese War","Seven Years' War","Peloponnesian War"]
    },
    "General Knowledge": {
      "question": "Top 10 tallest buildings in the world",
      "answers": ["Burj Khalifa","Shanghai Tower","Abraj Al-Bait Clock Tower","Ping An Finance Center","Lotte World Tower","One World Trade Center","Guangzhou CTF Finance Centre","Tianjin CTF Finance Center","Taipei 101","CITIC Tower"]
    },
    "Soccer": {
      "question": "Top 10 footballers by total club goals",
      "answers": ["Paolo Maldini","Francesco Totti","Roberto Baggio","Gianluigi Buffon","Alessandro Del Piero","Andrea Pirlo","Christian Vieri","Zlatan Ibrahimovic","Thierry Henry","Raul Gonzalez"]
    },
    "American Football": {
      "question": "Top 10 NFL defenders by career sacks",
      "answers": ["Lawrence Taylor","Reggie White","Bruce Smith","J.J. Watt","Deacon Jones","Von Miller","Chris Doleman","Derrick Thomas","Richard Dent","Jack Youngblood"]
    }
  },
  "2025-12-30": {
    "Geography": {
      "question": "Top 10 highest mountain ranges",
      "answers": ["Himalayas","Andes","Rockies","Alps","Urals","Caucasus","Atlas","Pyrenees","Carpathians","Great Dividing Range"]
    },
    "History": {
      "question": "Top 10 rulers by empire size (largest empires)",
      "answers": ["Genghis Khan","Alexander the Great","Julius Caesar","Napoleon Bonaparte","Queen Victoria","Charlemagne","Peter the Great","Catherine the Great","Abraham Lincoln","George Washington"]
    },
    "General Knowledge": {
      "question": "Top 10 world speed records (measured)",
      "answers": [
        "Speed of light – 299,792,458 m/s",
        "North American X-15 (aircraft) – ≈7,274 km/h",
        "ThrustSSC (land vehicle) – 1,228 km/h",
        "Spirit of Australia (watercraft) – 511 km/h",
        "JR-Maglev (train test) – 603 km/h",
        "Yangwang U9X (production car) – 496 km/h",
        "Peregrine Falcon – 389 km/h",
        "Sailfish – ≈110 km/h",
        "Cheetah – ≈120 km/h",
        "Usain Bolt – 44.72 km/h"
      ]
    },
    "Soccer": {
      "question": "Top 10 football clubs with the most goals scored in UEFA competitions",
      "answers": ["Real Madrid","Bayern Munich","Barcelona","Manchester United","Benfica","Juventus","Liverpool","Milan","Porto","Ajax"]
    },
    "American Football": {
      "question": "Top 10 NFL career statistical leaders (major categories)",
      "answers": ["Tom Brady (passing yards)","Emmitt Smith (rushing yards)","Jerry Rice (receiving yards)","Jerry Rice (receptions)","Adam Vinatieri (points scored)","Bruce Smith (sacks)","Ray Lewis (tackles)","Paul Krause (interceptions)","Tom Brady (career TDs)","Tom Brady (Super Bowl wins)"]
    }
  }
}

